He’s bad. She’s worse.
Problem Child 2 is a comedy, family film directed by Brian Levant.
Junior and his father, Ben, move from Cold River to Mortville.
Junior becomes threatened by Ben's desire to date again and find a new
mother for Junior, and sabotages each of his dates.
Ben Healy, played by John Ritter.
Junior Healy, played by Michael J. Oliver.
Big Ben Healy, played by Jack Warden.
LaWanda Dumore, played by Laraine Newman.
Annie Young, played by Amy Yasbeck.
Trixie Young, played by Ivyann Schwan.
Problem Child 2 is a 1991 American black comedy film and
a sequel to the 1990 film Problem Child.
The film stars John Ritter, Michael Oliver, Laraine
Newman, Amy Yasbeck, and Jack Warden.
Oliver reprises his role as Junior, an adopted orphan boy exploits who
deliberately wreaks comedic havoc everywhere he goes.
Ritter also reprises his role as his adopted father, Ben Healy.
Yasbeck, who played Ben's wife, Flo, from the first film, this time appearing as school nurse
Annie Young with a daughter named Trixie (Ivyann Schwan) who is also a problem child.
It was directed by Brian Levant in his feature film directorial debut and
produced by Robert Simonds, who also produced the first film.
In addition, Scott Alexander and Larry Karaszewski return as screenwriters.
It was rated PG-13, unlike its predecessor, which was rated PG.
While failing to match the success of the first film, Problem Child 2 was still a
box office success, doubling its budget in box office receipts.
The film explores themes of dark comedy, spoiled child,
slapstick comedy, problem child, vomiting.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.